The Richardsons were a normal family, they had lived
in the neighborhood all their lives.
His house had been passed down from generation to generation.
Young Jane Richardson was tired of
her quiet life, it was always the same
stories, nothing exciting ever happened in
that town.
One day, while daydreaming and looking
out the window, she saw a minivan loaded
with things park in the driveway of the house
across the street.
No one had lived there since old
Mr. Johnson had died years before.
“New neighbors,” Jane thought excitedly.
He saw a young man with
pale skin and brown hair wearing a
black and white striped T-shirt get out of the car.
Behind him was another boy, a little smaller.
They looked about his age.
They were quite cute, actually.
-Janeeee, dinner is ready!
The next morning, Jane went downstairs in her pajamas
to have breakfast. Her mother told her that the
Woods family had just moved, that they had two
children and that they would be going to the same school as her.
His mother always knew everything that was
happening.
Jane dressed up more than usual that day,
brushing her hair carefully, putting on her
favorite skirt and
knee-high socks.
He waited a few minutes at the door to see if
the two brothers would come out, but when he looked at
the clock he realized he was late and
had to rush out.
When he entered the classroom, Jeff was already
sitting there at the back desk.  He
looked sad, his gaze lost in
the window.  She
immediately felt like approaching him to
talk to him, but the bell rang,
classes were starting!
At lunchtime Jeff sat
without moving from his chair.
Jane wanted to introduce herself but her friends
dragged her into the dining room.
Aunt, Maikel hasn't invited me to the dance,
can you believe it?
Has anyone invited you yet?
Jane ignored what Steisi was saying, she
kept thinking about the new guy.
Aunt are you listening to me?  It
is important.
Yes, sorry.
I'm sure he'll ask you soon.
After finishing eating, Jane said goodbye to
her friends and went to the bathroom.  I did
n't want to keep hearing about the
Valentine's Day dance, which I didn't
have a partner for yet.
He walked down the long hallway of the lockers.
In the background, he saw Jeff putting something in his
locker, his head down.
When she returned home after
cheerleading practice, it was almost nighttime.  It
was pouring with rain and I didn't have an umbrella.  He
walked in his black boots, trying not to
step in the puddles.
Then, turning the corner, he found himself
in a violent situation.
Jeff was lying face down on the floor,
bleeding from his nose and lip.
All his clothes were soaked and dirty with mud
and blood.
At his side Randy, Troy and Jake emptied his
backpack in search of money.
What the [ __ ] is this!?  You
only have garbage.  We
should beat him so he learns
to carry valuables.
I'm getting wet for this jerk.
Let's go home Randy.
Randy gave him one last kick in the abdomen
before leaving.
Jane ran over and helped him up,
resting Jeff's head on her arms.  His
eyes were closed, he looked like he
had fainted.
Seeing his face Jane thought how sweet he
was and wiped the blood from his face.
Are you OK?
Does it hurt a lot?
Jeff opened his eyes and looked at her
closely.
His penetrating gaze made Jane blush.
He felt a tickling in his stomach and his
heart began to beat rapidly.
The sound of rain was interrupted by
Jeff's soft voice.
I'm better than ever," he finally said with
a smile that she returned.
He sat up somewhat dazed with his hand
on his stomach where he had received the kicks.
I'm Jeff, Jeff Woods.
I'm Jane, your neighbor.
Nice to meet you.
“Jeffrey Woods, you’re going to be mine,” she thought.
Thanks for your help Jane.
If you need anything, you can ask me.
Then Jane had an idea.  He
remembered the hateful Valentine's Day dance.
The date was approaching and she still hadn't
found anyone to accompany her.  It
would be a disaster to go alone, and although she was
embarrassed to ask him, she plucked up her courage.
You could accompany me to the dance.
If you don't have a partner, of course,
Jeff accepted somewhat surprised.
After the meeting, they became inseparable.
Jane loved being able to be with sweet
Jeff.
When they weren't together, she liked to watch him
through the window.
The days passed and the night of the dance arrived.
Jeff looked very handsome in his black suit and
red bow tie.
The color contrasted with his white skin and
gave him a very attractive look.
Jane was nervous.  She
had put on a red sequined dress
and black high heels.
They danced all night as if the rest of the
world didn't exist, she leaning on his shoulder
and he holding onto her waist until they melted
into a magical kiss.
(“So hot!”)
Suddenly Randy and his friends appeared.
They took Jeff outside and Jane ran
after them.
The boys wanted to beat him up.
Jeff flew into a rage and a sadistic smile and look
appeared on his face.  He
ended up killing two of them.  A
scared Randy covered him with bleach and alcohol
and set him on fire.
Jane felt powerless in the face of what was
happening.  He
grabbed the phone and called the police
just before he passed out.  He
woke up in the hospital next to his
parents and asked them:
What happened?
Is Jeff okay?
Don't talk about that boy again.
We forbid you from seeing him again.
- said his mother.
But Mom Jeff is special, you don't understand...
Enough Jane.  There is nothing
more to say.
Jane disobeyed orders, escaped and
searched for him in every room of the hospital.
He found him with his head bandaged.
“What happened to your beautiful face?”
But no matter how Jeff turned out,
she would still love him.
Once recovered they returned home.
Although Jane was forbidden to speak to him, she
continued to watch him through the window and
noticed that he was behaving
increasingly strangely.
“It’s like he’s not the same, that creepy
smile never leaves his face.”
“Has he forgotten about me?”
One night Jane woke up to the
sound of the door.  He went
downstairs and found a note in
the kitchen that read, "I haven't forgotten
about you.
No one can separate us now."
Frightened Jane grabbed a sharp knife.
She headed to the dining room where she found
her parents dead sitting at the table and
a terrible, ghastly, disfigured Jeff
waiting for her.
His once brown hair was now
black, his eyelids were burned, his
mouth was cut open, and he had the same sadistic look
as when he fought with Randy.
Jane cried out inconsolably.
Look who finally woke up.
Why are you making that face, Jane?
They had to go to sleep.
Don't worry, I'll make you look as beautiful
as me.
But what have you done, Jeff? Have you gone
crazy?
How could you?  I'll
kill you no matter what.
Jeff was no longer sweet Jeff.
He had become Jeff The Killer.  He
throws gasoline and bleach on Jane and
sets the whole house on fire.
When Jane woke up she was back in the
hospital, her head pounding, and a nurse
informed her that her family had died
in the fire.
When he saw himself in the mirror he was startled, his face
was completely burned.
Later a package arrived for Jane
containing a mask, a bouquet of black roses
and a sharp kitchen knife.  There
was a note: "Jane, I'm sorry you didn't
turn out as beautiful as me, but now we can
be together forever."
From that day on, Jane swore revenge for the
betrayal that resulted in the murder of her family.
How dare that damn Jeff take away
her loved ones?
Jane's motto is the opposite of Jeff's,
"Don't go to sleep," to prevent
Jeff from doing the same to more
innocent victims.
However, when the time comes... Will
Jane be able to erase the strong feelings she has
towards Jeff and carry out her revenge?
His best friend, his first love...
Can they be together again or
is it just the illusion of a sadistic lover?
Happy Valentine's Day, TikTokers!!
We hope you enjoyed this
Valentine's Day Special review of Jeff and Jane's story
. We had a great time making it.  Give
us lots of likes if you liked it and we'll be
encouraged to make more stories. See you
on Friday with a new video!!